{
    "subject": "resource/Sailing_at_the_2012_Summer_Olympics_\u2013_Laser",
    "predicate": "ontology/silverMedalist",
    "object": "resource/Pavlos_Kontides",
    "human_readable": "Pavlos Kontides won a silver medal in Sailing at the 2012 Summer Olympics.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9669254422187805,
            "question": "What color medal did Pavlos Kontides win at the 2012 Summer Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9208751320838928,
            "question": "In what year did Pavlos Kontides win a medal at the Summer Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9087452292442322,
            "question": "At which Olympic Games did Pavlos Kontides win a medal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7922408580780029,
            "question": "Was Pavlos Kontides successful in Sailing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7665136456489563,
            "question": "What event did Pavlos Kontides compete in at the Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.711193859577179,
            "question": "Is Pavlos Kontides a successful Olympian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7087251543998718,
            "question": "Did Pavlos Kontides win gold at the Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6155861616134644,
            "question": "What sport did Pavlos Kontides compete in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5272544622421265,
            "question": "What kind of athlete is Pavlos Kontides?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28070497512817383,
            "question": "What is Pavlos Kontides's nationality?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Pavlos Kontides won a silver medal in Sailing at the 2012 Summer Olympics.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7388_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of athlete is Pavlos Kontides?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7388_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What sport did Pavlos Kontides compete in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7388_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Pavlos Kontides win gold at the Olympics?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7388_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7388_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7388_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7388_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7388_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7388_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7388_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7388_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7388_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7388_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7388_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information, I can evaluate the triple as follows:\n\n* The subject is \"Pavlos Kontides\"\n* The predicate is \"won a silver medal in Sailing at the 2012 Summer Olympics\"\n* The answer to this query can be found by looking for documents that mention Pavlos Kontides and his achievements in sailing.\n\nUpon reviewing the context information, I find that all of the files (100.txt, 34.txt, 84.txt, etc.) contain information about Pavlos Kontides' achievements in sailing, including winning a silver medal at the 2012 Summer Olympics. Therefore, based on this evidence, the answer to the query is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Pavlos Kontides won a silver medal in the Laser sailing event at the 2012 London Olympics, which supports the given query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}